CHRISTOPHER POIRIER

UX DESIGNER VANCOUVER, BC



CONTACT

204-406-5358



hello@cpeartree.com



www.cpeartree.com



in www.linkedin.com/in/cpeartree

A New Media Design and Web Development student in pursuit of a challenging and rewarding UI/UX internship, utilizing my experience and education in user research, design, and testing to create intuitive and user-centred digital products that drive business success.

EDUCATION

New Media Design and Web Development British Columbia Institute of Technology 2021-2023

SKILLS

UI/UX Design

Digital Storytelling

Graphic Design

Project Management

Research

Account Management

Leadership

Sales

SOFTWARE

Figma

InDesign

XD

Final Cut Pro

Photoshop

HTML

Illustrator

CSS

HIGHLIGHTED PROJECT

UI/UX / APP DEVELOPMENT

Cato Weather | 2022

• School project focused on the development of a children's educational weather application. The project included creating a concept, researching market comparison, assessing market viability and designing wireframes.

EXPERIENCE

DU/ER | 2019-2020 SALES & SERVICE

- · Responsible for driving standard operating procedures, inventory management, and sales coaching/feedback.
- Growth of wholesale business & trade show presence
- Successfully assisted in the operations of the transition to a large-scale warehouse

Apple | 2012 - 2018 APPLE SOLUTIONS CONSULTANT

- Drove Apple's channel partner sales strategy in the Winnipeg and Vancouver markets.
- Engaged and supported store leadership teams on market strategy, while providing education and consultation to align sales teams with Apple's brand solutions.